<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<document>
	<properties>
		<title>Slim3</title>
	</properties>
	<body>
		<section name="Home">
			<p>
				Slim3 is a full-stack web application framework for agile development.
			</p>
			<p>
				Our main concept is "Simple" and <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Minimalism#Minimalist_design">"Less Is More"</a>.
				"Less is more" means simplicity and clarity lead to good design.
			</p>
			<p>
				80% of the effects come from 20% of the causes.
				We concentrate all our energies into 20% of the causes.
				Programmers can resolve the other issues without framework constraints.
			</p>
			<p>
				We want to get rid of complex and wasted features from your applications and our framework.
				As a result, we will slim down.
			</p>
			<p>
                Slim3 is a Java open source framework.
                The license is <a href="license.html">"The Apache Software License, Version 2.0"</a>.
            </p>
			<p>
				The main characteristics of Slim3 are as follows: 
				<ul>
				<li><a href="#HOT_deployment">HOT deployment</a></li>
				<li><a href="#Less_configuration">Less configuration</a></li>
				<li><a href="#Less_learning_cost">Less learning cost</a></li>
				</ul>
			</p>
			<subsection name="HOT deployment">
            <p>
                HOT deployment means re-deployment an application without restarting web application.
                Due to HOT deployment, you can see the result　as soon as you change the source code.
                The quick feedback is essence of agile development.
            </p>
            </subsection>
			<subsection name="Less configuration">
			<p>
				Do you want to write configuration files or not?
			</p>
			<p>
				Sure, you don't want to write them.
				Slim3 employs <b>Convention over Configuration(CoC)</b> and <b>Annotations</b> properly,
				so you don't need to write bloated configuration files.
			</p>
			<p>
			    If <b>CoC</b> is abused,
			    your source code will be hard to understand.
			    If <b>Annotations</b> is used too much,
                you will fall into <b>ANNOTATIONS HELL</b>.
                It is important to use <b>CoC</b> and <b>Annotations</b> properly.
			</p>
			</subsection>
			<subsection name="Less learing cost">
            <p>
                Slim3 is a thin wrapper on Struts 1.2 and JDBC.
                If you know them, you can learn Slim3 quickly.
                Many developers know Struts and JDBC.
                Slim3 is based on popular technologies.
            </p>
            <p>
                Furthermore, you can use Struts without bloated configuration files!!!
            </p>
            </subsection>
		</section>
	</body>
</document>